A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
A sound soul dwells within a sound body.
A sound body.
What?
It sets the mood.
Besides, it keeps the lines in my hair partially hidden.
No matter how many times I die it, those damn lines keep coming back.
Quite annoying.
Come on!
Here we are.
A station in the middle of the desert?
Let's get going.
The train will arrive any minute now.
You sound pretty excited about that.
How come?
That train has been operating on schedule for the last hundred years.
Never a second late or a second early.
How can I not be excited about seeing such a perfectly executed mode of transportation?
Right.
How silly of me.
Someone's already there.
It looks like a child.
Well, the train is famous, I guess.
Hello there.
Sure is hot today, isn't it?
Hello?
Whoa.
Hey, Magic!
Where are your manners?
Aren't you going to answer us?
When someone says hello, you answer, okay?
Calm down.
Hey!
Who do you think you are, clicking your tongue at us like that, huh?
That's it, I'm going to tell you!
Oh, wow.
Look at all the sand, Patty.
Why don't we sit here and play for a while?
Yeah!
I'm going to build a sand castle!
According to the schedule, the train should be arriving soon.
Is that why you're here?
The Runaway Express?
Chee, chee, chee!
All done!
Wow!
Looks great, Patty.
I don't know what it is, but there's something not quite right about that kid up there.
I still don't see anything.
At this rate, it's going to miss its scheduled arrival.
So its perfect punctuality was nothing more than a rumor.
How disappointing.
Aw, I fell down!
Aw.
Say hi.
Bye-bye.
Tsk.
the grim reaper sent his minions i see well you're too late this big fish is mine for the taking
the magic tool belongs to arachne fisher that's the agent arachne sent to get the tool
what
a witch's soul so that kid wasn't a tourist after all
though i suppose witches can be tourists too
that settles it tourists don't leave bombs
man that train can really move oh wow it looks like an earthwork you can admire it later right
now i need you to transform
there it is
i'm the first one aboard the magic tool is mine for the taking
impossible he's already caught up
watch out kids incoming missile 10 o'clock
do you like my fishing rod do you like my missiles how's that feel
how does that feel
what happened
i can use this to my advantage the smoke will hide my approach
kids the train's about to turn right
what now dodging attacks from both the side and above while trying to board a runaway train that
moves at 500 kilometers an hour is not easy patty can i leave this to you
i'll finish him as soon as he shows his ugly face he's all yours
oh
come out come out wherever you are
gotcha die fisher guy
360 degree kickflip
nice one
what are you doing kid this isn't the time to be showing off your skateboard skills
don't you know anything that was an incredible hill we ran over back there
given the situation it would have been wrong not to have done a trick or two on it
what look we've got another one coming up patty it's a no-hander
30 600
what are they doing up there
good now transform patty
yeah
i'm a sitting duck up here
there's no sign of the guy he must have gone up to the front
all i have to do is pull this lever and it's bye-bye to anyone in the cars behind me
all right where'd the guy run off to
got him you move fast skateboard kid but that won't keep you from blowing up along with this half of the
train
damn it he's going to uncouple the cars
that was close i forgot that i had to watch for attacks from the air too
but no one catches the fisher king
now avoiding that attack landed me on the wrong side of the train
this guy's a special kind of stupid
this guy's a special kind of stupid stupid stupid stupid seriously damn
thank you
and
Ahh!
We're flying!
How cool!
Dammit!
I can taste victory!
No one's getting into the engine room ahead of me!
Where is he going?
Liz, hurry.
Fishing rod launcher!
Die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die!
Geez, this guy is stupid, ugly and a bad shooter.
Die, die, die, die, die, die, die!
Hey!
Damn.
That's it.
The train's power source.
The magic tool.
Known as the Eternal Spring.
I've got it! You're too late!
Agh!
You can't have it!
It belongs to the witch around me!
This is what we came here for.
After it's gone, the runaway express will sleep.
This is an evil tool. Just holding it disgusts me.
I see you're a typical ignorant student of the Academy.
That tool was created by the great wizard Abon.
It's a work of genius.
What? Abon?
If he made this, he's an evil piece of trash.
Would you say that of Lord Death as well?
What does my father have to do with this?
Oh, how cute! So you're the Grim Reaper's son, are you?
Then let me show you something.
Open the box that held the Eternal Spring.
of genius what a bond if he made this he's an evil piece of trash would you say that of lord
death as well what does my father have to do with this oh how cute so you're the grim reaper's son
are you then let me show you something open the box that held the eternal spring and look inside
that box there what's in it that i need to see a punch tool isn't just the spring alone it also
includes the box you see there with the keyhole in it that's where you need to look go on open it
open it you know you want to read what's written on the plate inside the box
it says abon and then below that it says it says death there's no mistaking it that's dad's
handwriting why would dad's signature be on something evil like this what's wrong kid
yes what's wrong could it be you find what's written there in tab to stabbing whose signature
is it you see there on that evil tool what's the meaning of this tell me what's going on here
what's he doing here it's sid
i'll take care of the others with a collection squad from the african branch
you guys go get some rest
this soul belongs to you kid go ahead and take it
get it shoot it down
sit there was a witch here too she escaped our objective was the eternal spring
let the witch go okay kids you head on to the camp for some rest there will be cold drinks waiting for
you yay thank you mr awesome thanks yeah thanks
the objective has been completed the dwma has another magic tool
i'm not finding anything even remotely useful in the level one reference books
would you say that of lord death as well
who exactly is abon
yes may i help you is there a specific book you need
actually i'd like to see any materials that you have in the level four block regarding the person known as
abon
let me see your student id
i'm sorry i can't help you
students with up to two stars can check out books from the second level faculty can view all of level
three materials only death size and select high ranking meisters may access level four
four you are only a one star meister as such you may only check out books from the first level
take a look at the back of my card okay
please excuse me i didn't realize you were a member of lord death's family
i'll find the books you asked for immediately sir please wait here a moment thank you
i'm still only a one star meister i'd hope to have been much further along than that by now
if i ask dad straight out he'll brush me off like he did when i asked about the kishin
i have to find out myself
have you found it yes one book does match your request it contains information about abon great
can you please direct me to the shelf that it's on it's urgent unfortunately it seems that the book
was lent out two months ago and has not yet been returned do you know who borrowed it if necessary
i'll track down whoever it is myself and ask that they return it
again i'm deeply sorry sir due to insufficient records i do not know who is the last person to
check it out the signature line has no name on there's only the letter m nothing more i'm afraid
i'm very sorry please forgive my negligence in this
who besides me would have an interest in a book like that it was taken out of the library two months
ago on the first of april the day the kishin revived
m m was it medusa
so
uh
To與我合身的影響
Usoppily sing
Once you love me
One orders three
Things that trapped time
, I can take this 女性
I can save this
I can play game
свет there
Sir, for all the lights
This time is永遠, and now I'm going to cry.
This heart is a dream.
I'll see you next time.
I'll hear you next time.
The voice of our friends is like the same.
As in the wind of the city,
I'll never go back.
I'll trust you next time.
Ah!
Beautiful skin?
Choo-choo!
Excalibur's back in the next episode!
No, Patty.
Next time it's about the party.
Choo-choo!
Parties are fun!
Kong Kong!
Meow!
That's not what a train sounds like.
Choo-choo!
On the next episode of Soul Eater,
Drying Happiness,
whose tears sparkle in the moonlight?
Choo-choo!
What kind of preview is this?